halobeauty.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Halo Beauty Inc.

HaloBeauty.com (“Halo Beauty”) provides users with:

the www.HaloBeauty.com website (“Site”);

any online accounts, web-based applications or platforms made available for use on any device or technology platform (“Applications”); and

any of Halo Beauty’ products made available on the Site or via the Applications (“Services”).   The Site, Applications and Services are all facilities, functions or activities (“Features”) developed by us and designed to assist your experience.

Our central goal is to provide the best products and optimize your experience while using them. To make that work effectively, Halo Beauty needs to collect personal information from each customer and process that personal information.

Halo Beauty uses common technologies such as cookies and Web beacons to keep track of your interactions with the Site, Application and Services and to improve the quality of our products and services.

Halo Beauty may also collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address to track and aggregate non-personally identifiable information, your referring website addresses, browser type, domain name and access times.

Unless connected directly to a user account, the information Halo Beauty processes in connection with each IP address is largely statistical and is not stored to or referred to by Halo Beauty in a way that permits us to piece together any particular user’s browsing behavior. It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about how we processes information about you. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the Features operated by Halo Beauty or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. From time to time Halo Beauty may also post product or service specific privacy notices or documentation to explain in more detail how Halo Beauty handles information related to privacy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to access your information, please feel free to contact us at Support@HaloBeauty.com or write to us:

Halo Beauty, Inc.  
1905 Wilcox Ave., #111  
Los Angeles, CA  90068

**SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**

Information you provide – When you purchase a product from the Site or sign up for a service operated by Halo Beauty, you may be required to provide personal information (including, but not limited to, name, address, telephone or age) and other information which can be used to ascertain your idenity. Halo Beauty may combine the information you submit under your account with information from your activity on the Site for the purpose of providing you with a better experience and to improve the quality of Halo Beauty’ Features, products and services. For certain services, Halo Beauty may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. You can use your user account to learn more about the information associated with your Account.

Cookies – When you visit the Site, Halo Beauty may send one or more cookies to your computer or device. Halo Beauty uses cookies to improve the quality of Halo Beauty’ products and services, including for storing your preferences, improving search results, improving features and tracking your trends so that we can better service you.

Log information – When you access the Site, Halo Beauty’ servers may record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a product, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

Communications – When you send an email or other communications to Halo Beauty, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve Halo Beauty’ products or services. Halo Beauty may use your email address to communicate with you about Halo Beauty’ products or services.

Third Party Applications – Halo Beauty may make available third party applications through the Site, such as gadgets, extensions or payment gateways. The information collected by Halo Beauty is processed under this Privacy Policy when you enable a third party application. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their own privacy policies and we recommned that you read and understand their respective privacy policies. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located. As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Other sites – This Privacy Policy applies to the Site only. Halo Beauty does not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include Halo Beauty applications, products or services, or links from within Halo Beauty’ various Features. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

Email Marketing – With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

Google Analytics – Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

In addition to the above, Halo Beauty may use the information Halo Beauty collects to:

Provide, maintain, protect, and improve the Features, Halo Beauty’ services (including advertising services) and develop new products and services; and

Protect the rights or property of Halo Beauty or its users.

If Halo Beauty uses this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then Halo Beauty will ask for your consent prior to such use.

It is unlikey that Halo Beauty will disclose your personal information to other overseas recipients.

**SECTION 2 – CONSENT**

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

Your Choice to Opt Out

If you would like to opt-out from having Halo Beauty collect your information in connection with our products or services, please let us know by contacting us at Support@HaloBeauty.com or mailing us at:  
Halo Beauty, Inc.  
1905 Wilcox Ave., #111  
Los Angeles, CA  90068

Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**SECTION 3 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES, INFORMATION SHARING & ONWARD TRANSFER**

Halo Beauty only shares personal information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:

When Halo Beauty has your consent. We will usually require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

When Halo Beauty provides such information to its subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on Halo Beauty’ behalf such as payment gateways, fulfillment centers, and other payment transaction processors. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

When Halo Beauty has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to: satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; enforce our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations of those Terms; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Halo Beauty, its customers or the public as required or permitted by law.

If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets, we will use our best endeavors to: ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions; and provide notice before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**SECTION 4 – SECURITY**

Halo Beauty takes reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

Halo Beauty restricts access to personal information to its employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf.   These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and legal action criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**SECTION 5 – FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICES**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via in site notification within 7 business days.

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**SECTION 6 –** **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to communicate with you regarding your use of our products and or services.   If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at Support@halobeauty.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**SECTION 7 –   CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY ACT ******

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA we agree to that users can visit our site anonymously.

**SECTION 8 – COMPLAINTS**

When Halo Beauty receives formal written complaints, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns.   We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Halo Beauty and an individual.

**SECTION 9 – AGE OF CONSENT**

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13.  By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

**SECTION 10 –** **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

**SECTION 11 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).

**SECTION 12 – QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at Support@HaloBeauty.com or by mail at  
Halo Beauty, Inc.  
Attn:  Privacy Compliance   
1905 Wilcox Ave., #111  
Los Angeles, CA  90068
